ANGUS INNES

Product Manager

https://www.linkedin.com/in/angusinnes/

a.innes9@gmail.com UK# +44 7990 800 961

I have produced product and service design work for Jamie Oliver, Google and Tag Heuer and been a software engineer in a team that successfully planned and executed a cloud-services migration to AWS for the Home Office. With an understanding of technology, design and product-market fit I get involved at both design and delivery phases of projects. Excellent ability to communicate with different stakeholders including technical experts and senior product owners.

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Solutions Architect Associate
British Computing Society Certifications
(Business Change, Requirements Engineering, Systems Development and Testing)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Deloitte Digital (November 2016 - Present)

Technologies: Linux, ELK, AWS (S3, EC2, SES, CloudWatch), Terraform, MongoDB, RDS, Kibana, Scala, Play, Raspberry Pi

Deloitte Digital is a professional services firm focused on the delivery of digital transformations and commercial proof of concept for early stage technologies. I have spent the duration of my time at the company working for the Home Office, as such all titles listed below were for this client. We worked a form of agile using Kanban enabled by JIRA across teams comprised of both on and offshore workers.

Live Services Manager/Engineer (January 2018 - Present)

As part of a team of two I managed the live services desk for a service with over 2 million applicants a year. This meant resolving a course of action for time sensitivity priority applicants, triaging the cause of bugs or faults in production and implementing tactical and strategic fixes to ensure a high level of service was maintained for customers.

- Triaging application level issues relating to integration points with third party payment systems, email and appointment booking
- Managing high profile product owners by explaining incidents origin, cause and fix
- Making operational code changes of high value to the business, such as time-based switching of product pricing, managing how customers were informed of this change and ensuring successful testing
- Enacting the continuous deployment process, from managing cut and release notes to canary deployment

Devops Engineer (November 2016 - January 2018)

Aided in the migration of an entire live system between two cloud providers to AWS. Architecting and building automated, dockerized build and deployment pipelines.

- I was the lead responsible for the migration passing all operational acceptance testing
- To ensure telemetry at application and hardware level I implemented our logging and monitoring solution with use of Zabbix and the ELK stack, managing our applications integration into a platform wide solution
- Devised backups and restoration method across a replica set using AWS S3 and mongodb restore
- Architected and built automated, dockerized build and deployment pipelines to enable our continuous integration and delivery pipeline and create a new basis for the project using immutable infrastructure

and configuration as code for our new container-based stack

• I led retrospectives and organised team lunches fortnightly after identifying a need for a separate forum to address issues in the team before they arose in an environment of high stress - we were a composite of mixed experience that was scaling fast and facing hard deadlines

AKQA, London (January 2016 – July 2016)

AKQA is an International Advertising Agency specialising in digital product and service design Future Academy Member

Methods: Google Design Sprints, IDEO Double Diamond, Kanban, UX, Presentation, Design Future Academy was a client-winning initiative to showcase innovation within AKQA

- As a project manager and creative I delivered work for Tag Heuer, Jamie Oliver and Google Tensorflow
- Designed concepts, created and user-tested prototypes, from sketches to interactive apps
- Presented back to client for diverse products and services and to over 400 people at all company meeting

NOTABLE INTERNSHIPS

Selco Foundation, Bangalore (March 2015)

 Worked within a team to build a framework used by the World Wildlife Fund for means-testing entering energy access in geographic areas across India

The Bakery/Saatchinvest, London (October 2014)

- Shadowed Saatchinvest chief investor, the VC fund of M&C Saatchi, gaining exposure to London start up ecosystem and a corporate to startup matchmaking service at The Bakery
- Aided Unilever to understand a consumer issue and matched them to 4 potential start-ups with capability to solve their specific consumer problems

EDUCATION

General Assembly, Web Development Immersive, 2015-2016

GA WDI is a 12 week bootcamp that teaches students how to code and build web apps. I learnt Javascript, Node, Angular, Ruby, Rails, Postgres and Mongo, REST, MVC and thus produced 4 projects as applied testament to these taught skills. My website showcasing the work from this time is available at http://beruti.github.io/ as is the work on github.

B.A. Economics and Business Management, Newcastle University, 2.1

NOTED HOBBIES

- Principle Organiser and Treasurer a Caledonian Society ball for 400 people at University
- 3rd at Techstars StartUp Weekend for Social Impact 2018
- Next Steps Business Mentor at The Princes Trust
- Ran New Forest Marathon last year to raise £1000 for the mental health charity Sane
- Came last in the Lada Rally 2018, from Estonia to Greece we raised over £1000 for refugee charities and donated a BMW 3 series to those working in temporary settlement camps outside Thessaloniki
- Extensive Traveller

LANGUAGES

English (Native)
Spanish (Limited Working Proficiency)